{
    "translations": {
      "en": {
        "q0": {
          "type": "multiple",
          "question":"What is transition from state $\\{$q3$, $q4$\\}$ with the alphabet a. Select the appropriate state:",
          "description": "hello world",
          "answer": "q4",
          "choices": ["q0, q1, q2", "q1, q2, q3","q1, q5, q6" ,"q4"]
        },
        "q1": {
          "type": "multiple",
          "question":"What is the transition from state {q3, q4} with the alphabet b. Select the appropriate state:",
          "answer": "q1, q5, q6",
          "choices": ["q0, q1, q2", "q1, q2, q3","q1, q5, q6" ,"q4"]
        },
        "q2": {
          "type": "multiple",
          "question":"What is transition from state {q1, q5, q6} with the alphabet a. Select the appropriate state:",
          "answer": "q3",
          "choices": ["q0, q1, q2", "q1, q2, q3","q3, q4, q5" ,"q3"]
        },
        "q3": {
          "type": "multiple",
          "question":"What is the transition from state {q1, q5, q6} with the alphabet b. Select the appropriate state:",
          "answer": "No Transition",
          "choices": ["q0, q1, q2", "q1, q2, q3","q1, q5, q6" ,"No Transition"]
        },
        "q4": {
          "type": "multiple",
          "question":"What is the transition from state {q3} with the alphabet a?",
          "answer": "No Transition",
          "choices": ["q4", "q1, q2, q3","q5, q1" ,"No Transition"]
        },
        "q5": {
          "type": "multiple",
          "question":"What is the trnsition from state {q3} with the alphabet b?",
          "answer": "q5, q1",
          "choices": ["q6","q5, q1", "q1, q5, q6","No transition"]
        },
        "q6": {
          "type": "multiple",
          "question":"What is the transition from state {q4} with the alphabet a?",
          "answer": "q6",
          "choices": ["q6", "q1, q2, q3","q5, q1" ,"No Transition"]
        },
        "q7": {
          "type": "multiple",
          "question":"What is the trnsition from state {q4} with the alphabet b?",
          "answer": "No transition",
          "choices": ["q6","q5, q1", "q1, q5, q6","No transition"]
        },
        "q8": {
          "type": "multiple",
          "question":"What is the transition from state {q5, q1} with the alphabet a?",
          "answer": "q3",
          "choices": ["q3", "q1, q2, q3","q5, q1" ,"No transition"]
        },
        "q9": {
          "type": "multiple",
          "question":"What is the trnsition from state {q5, q1} with the alphabet b?",
          "answer": "No transition",
          "choices": ["q3","q5, q1", "q1, q5, q6","No transition"]
        },
        "q10": {
          "type": "multiple",
          "question":"What is the transition from state {q6} with the alphabet a?",
          "answer": "No transition",
          "choices": ["q6", "q1, q2, q3","q5, q1" ,"No transition"]
        },
        "q11": {
          "type": "multiple",
          "question":"What is the trnsition from state {q6} with the alphabet b?",
          "answer": "No transition",
          "choices": ["q3","q5, q1", "q1, q5, q6","No transition"]
        },
        "q12notUSed": {
          "type": "iframe",
          "src": "../../../AV/FLA/billyu/ui/FAFixer.html",
          "question":"What is the final state?",
          "answer": "q1, q2, q3",
          "choices": ["q0, q1, q2", "q1, q5, q6","q4" ]
        },
        "q13": {
          "type": "select",
          "question":"What are the final state? Note that, any state that include states $q5$ or $q6$ should be a final state",
          "answer": ["q5, q1", "q1, q5, q6", "q6"],
          "choices": ["q0, q1, q2", "q3, q4","q4", "q1, q5, q6", "q3", "q6", "q5, q1"]
        }
      }
    }
  }
  